https://www.optimedhealth.com/privacy-policy/

GAP Solutions
What Is GAP?
Limited Medical
Limited Medical Plans
EMPLOYERS
What Is GAP?
OptiMed Privacy Policy
At OptiMed the privacy of our visitors is very important to us.
Our policy is to collect personal information (name, address, phone, email address, etc.) only when it is necessary for the proper execution of a service we offer. This information is obtained on a voluntary basis when a visitor submits a form on our site. The information collected is solely for the purposes of providing you with the best service possible.
It is not our policy to share or sell any personal information we may collect with a third party unless it is necessary for the proper execution of a service that a visitor has requested or the visitor has given us permission to do so.
NEWSLETTERS
OptiMed's newsletters are optional benefits for clients and newsletter subscribers to update you with the latest OptiMed news, program updates. At any time, you may request that OptiMed not send further promotional materials by contacting us via email at sales@optimedhealthplans.com.
TRACKING
This website may at any time employ Google Ads remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. This is accomplished by placing a small section of code on your device. This text snippet does not in anyway identify you nor does it provide access to your device. Google Ads remarketing enables us to tailor ads to the interests you indicated by visiting this site.
This site also uses tracking code supplied by social media sites that compile lists on their platforms of those who clicked a link from them to this site. This neither reveals your identity nor your email address; it only enables us to advertise to you on the specific social media platform.
COOKIES
The OptiMed website may use “cookies” to help personalize your visit to this site. A cookie is a text file placed on your hard disk by a web page server. A cookie from this website cannot run programs nor deliver viruses to your device. Cookies are assigned exclusively to you, and can be read only by the web server that issued it.
The purpose of a cookie is to save you time by offering to auto fill form fields on subsequent visits with information your provided previously.
POLICY CHANGES
OptiMed reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, but we will not do so without posting the modified Privacy Policy on our web site. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email and users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.
LINKS
This site contains links to other sites. OptiMed is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with OptiMed. IN NO EVENT WILL OPTIMED BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE, OR ON ANY OTHER HYPER LINKED WEB SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE ARE EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using this site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of the OptiMed privacy policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy, you may not use this web site. Your continued use of our web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
The OptiMed program is not available in the State of Washington and State of Montana. Please check with your OptiMed sales representative to confirm that OptiMed is available in the state or states in which you may have an interest in offering OptiMed.
